export const cards = [
  {
    front: 'What is the rotation interval for AWS-managed KMS keys?',
    back: '1 year',
  },
  {
    front: 'What AWS service can be used to audit a KMS Key usage?',
    back: 'CloudTrail',
  },
  {
    front: 'What is the maximum execution duration for an Express Step Function?',
    back: '5 minutes',
  },
  {
    front: 'What infrastructure creation tool is utilized by AWS SAM?',
    back: 'CloudFormation',
  },
  {
    front: 'What is the maximum execution duration for a Standard Step Function?',
    back: '1 year',
  },
  {
    front: 'Where are AWS CodeBuild artifacts stored?',
    back: 'S3',
  },
  {
    front: 'How can you enable different origins from making requests to your API Gateway?',
    back: 'Enable CORS',
  },
  {
    front: 'What property can you use to get only specified fields from a DynamoDB query?',
    back: 'ProjectionExpression',
  },
  {
    front: 'What is the maximum execution duration for a Lambda function?',
    back: '15 minutes',
  },
  {
    front: 'What is the simplest way to delete old items from a DynamoDB table?',
    back: 'Set a TTL',
  },
  {
    front: 'What is the default concurrency limit for Lambda functions in an AWS account for the same region?',
    back: '1000',
  },
  {
    front: `
What is the maximum number of concurrent executions that can be reserved for all Lambda functions in a region + account combination 
using the default concurrency limit?`,
    back: '900',
  },
];
